我是布罗克
This is Brock.
有间很老的狩猎小屋
There's an old hunting cabin up here.
我去看看
I'm gonna go check it out.
收到
Copy.
你要等待支援吗
Do you want to wait for backup?
不用  看起来没人
Negative. Looks abandoned.
我操
Holy shit.
胡德
Hood.
黑吃黑
第四季
第一集
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
我没有
I didn't.
我是说  我不是在找你
I mean, I wasn't looking for you.
我以为你远走高飞了
I thought you were gone.
嘿  帮帮忙
Hey, you want to do me a favor
别拿那玩意儿指着我行吗
and point that thing somewhere else, okay?
天啊
Holy hell.
两年没见了
Haven't seen you in two years.
你一直住这小屋里
And all that time you've been living up in this cabin
跟野人一样吗
like some kind of mountain man or something?
有人跟你一起吗
Is there anybody here with you?
没有
No.
那你需要跟我走
Then I'm gonna need you to come with me.
不要
No.
我不是请求你
I'm not asking.
-洛特斯警长  -没错
- Sheriff Lotus. - That's right.
感觉如何
How does that feel?
跟痔疮一样
Like a hemorrhoid.
要告诉我是怎么了吗
You want to tell me what this is about?
回局里告诉你
I'll tell you down at the station.
你是指凯迪吗
You mean the Cadi?
不  我不是指那里
No. No, I don't.
女妖镇欢迎你  请小心驾驶
女妖镇警局
你觉得如何
What do you think?
防弹玻璃
Bulletproof glass.
1.5英寸厚的聚碳酸酯
One-and-a-half- inch-thick polycarb.
你应该会喜欢
Thought you'd like that.
斯格特  指纹检查结果你拿到后马上给我
Scott, I need those fingerprint results as soon as you get them.
-好的  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
我要知道记者会的事
I need to know about the press conference.
邦克  还记得胡德先生吗
Bunker, you remember Mr. Hood?
妮娜·克鲁兹副警长
Deputy Nina Cruz.
比利·雷文升职了  他是奇诺警署的新警长
Billy Raven moved on. He's the new chief of the Kinaho PD.
-警长  -海伦  有留言吗
- Sheriff. - Helen, any messages?
在您桌子上
On your desk.
-联调局那边呢  -还没有回应
- Oh, the FBI? - Not yet.
-办公室不错  -是的
- Nice office. - Yes, it is.
你要喝点什么吗
Can I get you something to drink?
我这里有水  咖啡  我这里有台咖啡机
I got water, coffee. I've got this espresso machine here.
坐吧
Have a seat.
首先  你需要知道
First of all, you should know
我今天去那里时
when I went up there today,
根本没想到会找到你
you were the last person I expected to find.
两天前你在那个小屋里吗
Were you in that cabin two nights ago?
在
Yes.
-还有别人吗  -没有
- Anybody with you? - No.
谁死了
Who's dead?
那是谁
Who is that?
丽贝卡
Rebecca.
她的尸体昨天在河边发现
Her body was found yesterday near the river.
她不是在那儿遇害的
That's not where she was killed,
但尸体被抛在了那里
but that's where the body was dumped.
天啊
Jesus.
这是今年发生的第三起类似谋杀案了
This is the third murder of its kind that we've had this year.
-你通知了联调局  -对
- You call the FBI? - Yeah.
第二起发生后我就通知了
I called them after the second one
他们派了一个小混蛋过来
and they sent some little shit up here
他看了我们的档案  做了些笔记
and he looked through our files and took some notes
然后就赶着投胎似的
and then he ran back to Quantico
踩着60块的破鞋跑回了匡蒂科
as fast as his little $60 loafers could take him.
告诉我如果发生第三起再打电话过去
Told me to call back if a third body turned up.
所以现在他们可能会重视了
So maybe now they'll give a shit.
那这跟我有什么关系
So what does this have to do with me?
你最后一次见丽贝卡是什么时候
When was the last time you saw Rebecca?
我已经有18个月
I haven't seen anyone
没见过别人了
for about 18 months.
但这就奇怪了
And yet, it's the weird part,
是她车载GPS最后的定位
the last coordinates on her car's GPS
今天把我带到了你的小屋
brought me up to your cabin today.
-你没见到她  -没有
- You didn't see her? - Nope.
你知道她为什么要来找你吗
Any idea why she'd come looking for you?
她怎么会知道你在那里  胡德
How the hell she'd even know you were up there, Hood?
我只想捋清楚这事
I'm just trying to put this together.
-那是她叔叔的地  -那是什么
- It's her uncle's land. - It's what?
那是她叔叔的地
It's her uncle's land.
你住在普罗科特的地方
You're living on Proctor's land?
他不知道
He doesn't know.
你遇到什么事了  胡德
What happened to you, Hood?
我退休了
I retired.
我们发现了少量与丽贝卡血型不符的血迹
We found trace blood that didn't match Rebecca's.
我需要你自愿提供一份血样
I'm gonna need you to voluntarily submit a blood sample
供我们排除嫌疑
so we can rule you out.
你现在怀疑我是连环杀人犯了
You think I'm a fucking serial killer now?
你最近照过镜子吗  胡德
Have you seen yourself lately, Hood?
你住在树林里
You're living up in the woods.
看起来像个炸弹杀手
You look like the Unabomber.
-好  我可以提供血样  -还有  胡德
- Yes, you can have my blood. - Oh, and, Hood...
如果还有什么想告诉我的
If there's anything else you want to tell me,
就现在说吧
now's the time.
你应该盯着点普罗科特
You should be looking at Proctor.
是  但现在这事更复杂了
Yeah, well, these days that's a little more complicated.
他...
He's--
进来
Yeah?
媒体见面会要开始了
Press conference is about to start.
该死  好吧好吧
Oh, shit, yeah, yeah.
-知道了  -胡德警长
- Okay. - Sheriff Hood.
他不是警长
He's not the sheriff.
听着  我会让克鲁兹副警长来给你采血
Listen, I'll have Deputy Cruz come up and take your blood
然后她会送你回去
and then she'll give you a lift back.
你多保重
Take care of yourself.
怎么称呼
And you are?
有什么问题吗
Is there something wrong?
抱歉  你只是...
Sorry, you just--
刚才有个瞬间  你让我想起了一个人
you reminded me of someone for a moment.
被杀的副警长吗
Mmm, the deputy who got killed?
印第安小混混把她的脖子扭断了
Indian gangbanger broke her neck?
你不说话的时候我更喜欢你
I think I like you better when you don't talk.
先生  先生
Sir. Sir.
到时间了
It's time.
市长先生  这是今年第三起
Mr. Mayor, this is the third murder
针对年轻女性的谋杀案了
of a young woman this year.
这是个连环杀手吗
Is this a serial killer?
最近的受害人真的是您侄女吗
Is it true that the latest victim was your niece?
市长先生  为什么警方迟迟不发布公告
Mr. Mayor, why are the police reports being withheld?
据我们所知
Here's...here's what we know.
Here's what we know.
昨天  丽贝卡·鲍曼的尸体
Yesterday the body of Rebecca Bowman
在代尔伍德流域被发现
was found near the mouth of the Dellwood Basin.
最新美劇下載
www.ZiMuZu.tv
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
她是被谋杀的
She was murdered.
虽然警方无法确定
And while the police can't say for certain,
但这个案件与过去一年内发生的
there are definitely similarities between this case
两起年轻女子被杀案
and the murders of two other young women
确实有相似之处
that occurred over the last year.
女妖镇警局已经联系了联调局
The Banshee Sheriff's Department has notified the FBI
m 330 133 l 343 133 l 343 125 l 330 125 m 330 122 l 343 122 l 343 115 l 330 115 m 330 112 l 343 112 l 343 104 l 330 104 m 322 136 l 322 133 l 327 133 l 327 101 l 346 101 l 346 133 l 350 133 l 350 136 m 316 121 b 316 121 316 121 316 121 b 316 121 320 121 323 121 b 323 121 323 123 323 123 b 318 124 315 124 311 125 l 311 122 b 311 122 317 114 317 114 b 317 114 317 114 317 114 b 316 113 310 115 310 115 l 310 112 b 310 112 317 99 317 99 l 320 100 b 317 105 316 107 314 112 b 313 112 314 112 313 112 b 320 112 322 105 322 105 l 325 107 b 325 107 316 121 316 121 m 310 131 b 313 131 318 130 324 129 l 324 131 b 319 132 315 133 310 134 m 296 126 b 296 125 293 124 293 123 l 288 123 l 288 126 m 281 123 b 280 123 277 126 277 126 l 285 126 l 285 123 m 276 116 l 298 116 l 298 113 l 276 113 m 276 111 l 298 111 l 298 109 l 276 109 m 291 99 l 294 99 l 294 101 l 306 101 l 305 104 l 294 104 l 294 106 l 291 106 l 291 104 l 282 104 l 282 106 l 279 106 l 279 104 l 268 104 l 268 101 l 279 101 l 279 98 l 282 98 l 282 101 l 291 101 m 268 120 l 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 280 119 l 272 119 l 272 106 l 301 106 l 301 118 l 287 118 b 285 118 284 119 283 120 l 305 120 l 305 123 l 297 123 b 299 123 297 123 307 128 b 306 128 307 128 305 131 b 301 128 300 128 300 128 l 300 130 b 300 134 297 135 297 135 l 291 135 b 291 135 291 135 291 132 b 291 132 291 133 291 133 b 292 132 292 132 297 132 b 297 130 297 130 297 131 l 297 129 l 288 129 l 288 138 l 285 138 l 285 129 l 277 129 l 277 136 l 274 136 l 274 127 b 274 127 274 127 268 131 b 268 131 268 131 266 129 b 266 129 272 125 276 123 l 268 123 m 244 98 l 244 98 b 244 98 246 103 247 104 l 244 104 l 263 104 l 263 112 l 259 112 l 259 108 l 229 108 l 229 113 l 225 113 l 225 104 l 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 241 99 m 242 119 l 251 115 l 231 115 l 231 112 l 256 112 l 256 116 l 246 121 l 246 122 l 264 122 l 264 125 l 246 125 l 246 129 b 246 134 246 137 243 138 l 235 138 b 235 138 234 134 234 134 b 236 134 236 134 242 134 b 242 134 242 130 242 130 l 242 125 l 224 125 l 224 122 l 242 122 m 210 58 l 192 58 l 192 54 l 210 54 m 225 55 l 239 56 l 261 28 l 245 28 l 225 53 b 224 49 221 45 216 46 l 178 46 l 178 66 l 193 66 l 193 77 l 189 77 l 191 68 l 178 68 l 174 87 l 188 87 l 190 81 l 193 87 l 209 87 l 209 66 l 225 66 m 192 19 l 210 19 l 210 21 l 192 21 m 192 9 l 210 9 l 210 12 l 192 12 m 228 34 l 210 34 l 209 31 l 226 31 l 226 27 l 238 27 l 261 0 l 244 0 l 226 22 l 225 22 l 225 6 b 225 3 224 0 217 0 l 177 0 l 176 30 l 193 30 l 193 34 l 174 34 l 174 43 l 227 43 m 246 57 l 226 79 l 224 69 l 212 69 l 215 85 l 223 84 l 222 87 l 238 87 l 261 57 m 336 77 l 336 59 l 329 58 l 329 14 l 315 14 l 315 49 l 291 87 l 306 87 l 324 58 l 324 87 l 346 87 l 350 77 m 310 10 l 334 10 l 335 56 l 345 56 l 345 6 b 345 4 343 0 339 0 l 298 0 l 298 56 l 310 56 m 295 36 l 286 36 l 295 21 l 295 10 l 288 10 l 284 0 l 267 0 l 272 10 l 261 10 l 261 20 l 279 20 l 260 51 l 270 51 l 270 86 l 283 87 l 283 42 l 285 39 l 287 64 l 297 64 m 155 87 l 129 35 l 104 87 l 84 87 l 128 0 l 146 0 l 132 30 l 146 30 l 174 87 m 66 87 l 39 35 l 14 87 l -5 87 l 38 0 l 56 0 l 42 30 l 56 30 l 84 87 m 203 138 l 199 138 l 190 111 l 194 111 l 201 133 b 201 134 201 134 201 133 l 209 111 l 213 111 m 188 135 l 188 137 b 183 137 188 137 183 137 b 183 137 179 138 179 134 l 179 115 l 176 115 l 176 111 l 179 111 l 179 104 l 183 103 l 183 111 l 187 111 l 187 115 l 183 115 l 183 135 b 183 135 183 135 188 135 m 166 132 l 171 132 l 171 137 l 166 137 m 154 111 l 158 111 l 158 137 l 155 137 l 155 133 b 153 136 151 138 145 137 b 143 138 139 137 136 132 l 136 111 l 140 111 l 140 127 b 140 131 139 134 146 135 b 151 135 153 132 154 128 m 110 134 l 132 134 l 132 137 l 104 137 l 104 135 l 126 105 l 107 105 l 107 102 l 131 102 l 131 105 m 96 111 l 100 111 l 100 137 l 97 137 l 97 133 b 94 135 93 138 88 138 b 85 138 81 136 79 130 l 79 111 l 83 111 l 83 130 b 84 133 86 135 89 135 b 94 135 97 130 96 123 m 69 107 l 57 137 l 54 137 l 42 107 l 42 137 l 38 137 l 38 102 l 43 102 l 56 132 l 67 102 l 73 102 l 73 137 l 69 137 m 27 111 l 31 111 l 31 137 l 27 137 m 27 102 l 31 102 l 31 106 l 27 106 m 0 135 l 23 135 l 23 137 l -5 137 l -5 135 l 17 105 l -3 105 l -3 102 l 22 102 l 22 104
探员们正在前来协助调查的路上
and agents are en route to assist in the investigation.
关于你的问题
And to answer your question,
没错  丽贝卡是我的侄女
yes, Rebecca was my niece.
还有  是的  你们可以放心
And, yes, you can rest assured
我  洛特斯警长  还有他局里的人
that neither I nor Sheriff Lotus
不找到这个病态又扭曲的混蛋
and the members of his department will rest
绝不会罢休
until we have found this sick, twisted bastard.
十二个月前
就是这里吗
So this is it?
对  就是这里
Yes, this is it.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
我将成为市长
I'm going to be mayor
而生意上你要多管一点
and you're taking on more of a leadership role in the business.
我只是觉得我们需要多一层保障
I just figured we'd need something a bit more secure.
你喜欢这里吗
Do you like it?
太爱了
I love it.
出来
Get out.
怎么回事
What's going on?
地方检察官撤回起诉了  你可以走了
DA dismissed the charges. You're free to go.
你在耍我们
You're fucking with us.
过十秒你再不走  我就把门关上
You got 10 seconds before I close that door again.
我就知道你们不该抓我
I knew that arrest was bullshit.
这次又怎么了
What was it this time?
物证
Physical evidence.
他们差一点勒死那个老头
They practically strangled that old man.
我知道  地方检察官太有才了
I know. DA's a real piece of work.
他就是个傀儡
He's a puppet.
普罗科特操控着他
Proctor's got his hand up his ass.
下次再说这事
But that's a talk for another time.
隔墙有耳
The walls have ears.
非常感谢  警官  祝你愉快
Hey, thanks a lot, Officer. Have a nice evening.
我总是禁不住在想他
There's always some part of me that's thinking about him.
他死时的样子
How he looked when he died.
他看着我时的样子
How he looked at me.
有时候那段记忆会困扰我
There are days when that look haunts me
以至于无法呼吸
so badly I can barely breathe.
嘿  看那里
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Look at this.
有时我可以让自己分心不去想
And then there are days when I can distract myself.
你迷路了吗  宝贝
You lost, honey?
我可以屏蔽所有的噪音
Where I can shut off all the noise.
也许我们可以帮你
Maybe we can help you find your way.
那最好了
Oh, I hope so.
我只做我需要做的事
And just do what I have to do.
那样的日子就挺好
Those are the good days.
你们这些壮汉喜欢欺负人  是吧
So you tough guys like beating up on people, huh?
不是我们干的  警察让我们走了
It wasn't us. They let us go.
他们真不应该
Well, they shouldn't have.
有时当我刚醒来时总会觉得
There's always that moment when I just wake up
自己还在那里
where I think I'm still there,
在我们的老房子里
still back there in our old house.
但我转过身时
And when I roll over,
戈登会在我身边躺着
Gordon will be there lying next to me.
然后我会听见孩子们在他们的房间打闹
And then I'll hear the kids stirring in their rooms.
你是如何解压的呢
So how do you handle it?
锻炼
I exercise.
吃些东西
I eat something.
开始打理房子
I start working on the house.
房子如何能帮到你
How's the house coming along?
我做手工时
There's something about working with my hands
可以得到宁静
that gives me peace.
还有什么让你平静
What else gives you peace?
没什么了
Not much.
你觉得这个疗程有用吗
Do you find our sessions helpful?
我来这里只是因为是法庭强制的
I'm here because it's court-mandated.
无意冒犯
No offense.
没事
None taken.
如果我今天担保了你抚养孩子的资格
If I vouch for your competency to parent your children today,
你还会再来吗
would you come back?
如果我说是你会那么做吗
If I said yes, would you do that?
事情其实不是这样的
That's not really how it works.
他们无权带走我的孩子们
They had no right to take my kids away.
你违反了缓刑期的条例
You violated the terms of your probation.
我被挟持了
I was abducted.
军方的调查已经澄清了
The military investigation cleared us.
任何和犯罪有关的要素
Any association with the criminal element
-对于社会福利部门已经足够  -我知道
- was enough for social services - I know.
我知道
I know.
十七个月前
你要毁了我们的生活多少次
How many times are you gonna ruin our lives?
从今以后  你只是把我妈肚子搞大的混蛋
From now on, you're just the asshole who knocked up my mom.
求你了
Please.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
经理告诉我我们的前警长在酗酒
The manager told me our former sheriff was on a bender.
搞乱房间
Trashing the room.
玩枪
Playing with guns.
关你什么事
How is that your business?
这是我叔叔的汽车旅馆
It's my uncle's motel.
让我一个人待着  可以吗
Just leave me alone, would you?
快滚开  滚
Get the fuck out of here! Go!
求你走吧
Please go.
你不能待在这里
You can't stay here.
我带你回你家吧
Let me take you back to your place.
不  我再不能住那里了
No, I can't live there anymore.
那有鬼魂
There's ghosts.
这地方都被你弄成这样  没法住了
Even before you wrecked it, this dump is nowhere to live.
来吧  带你去个地方
Come on. Let's go for a ride.
这是个旧的狩猎木屋
It's an old hunting cabin.
很多年没用了  但还通水
Hasn't been used in years, but the water still runs.
这屋子是谁的
Whose is it?
你觉得是谁的
Who do you think?
你真觉得你叔叔会让我住在这里吗
You really think your uncle is gonna let me stay here?
他不会知道的
He won't know.
喜欢这里吗
How do you like it?
是的
Yeah.
就知道你会喜欢
I thought you would.
没有鬼魂
No ghosts.
-这里痛吗  -现在不了
- Does this hurt? - Not anymore.
我讨厌他们对你这么做
I hate that they did this to you.
反正我早就想弄掉这个纹身了
I had been meaning to get that tattoo removed anyway.
真希望可以永远这样
Just wish it could always be like this.
也许某天会的
Maybe one day.
你还好吗
You okay?
不
No.
站那儿别动  他马上就出来
Hang on right there. He'll be with you in a moment.
贱货
You fuck.
我们和红骨帮有严格的协议
We have a strict agreement with the Redbones.
你们在居留地里做生意
You keep your business on the reservation
我们也不会越界
and we keep ours off it.
你们违反了协议
You are in breach of that agreement.
什么事
Yeah?
我才刚开始工作  该死
I just got to work, for fuck's sake.
谁在那
Who's there?
靠
Shit.
不  好  什么事都别做
No. Okay. Don't do a fucking thing.
我马上回去
I'm coming back to town.
你可以自己问他
Well, you can ask him yourself.
这里一切都进展得很顺利
Things are going fantastic over here.
这次你请客  好的
This time you're buying. Okay.
行  行  行
All right, all right, all right.
很好  帮我向卡罗尔问好
Great. Say hi to Carol for me.
好啊  加尔文  有什么能帮到你的吗
Hey there, Calvin. What can I do you for?
我身体不太舒服  我需要回家
I'm not feeling great. I'm gonna need to go home.
-你看着挺好的啊  -我胃痛
- You look fine. - I've got a stomach bug.
我以为我能熬过今天  可我不行
I thought I could make it through the day, but I can't.
你负责三季刊  是吧
You're handling the triquarterlies, aren't you?
弄完了吗
They done?
还没
Not yet, no.
我今天就要
Kind of need those done today.
我可以带回家做
Well, I can take them home with me
明天一大早就交给你
and I'll have them done for you first thing tomorrow.
上个季度我们也迟了  对吗
We were late with them last quarter, too, weren't we?
没有吧
I don't think so, no.
我觉得有  加尔文
I think we were, Calvin.
我操你妈
Gook motherfucker!
明天一大早就给你
I'll have those to you first thing tomorrow.
他在这做什么
What the fuck is he doing here?
我们进来就看到他
We came in and found him here
还有这个被夹在虎头钳里的贱逼
with this motherfucker already in the vise.
他在我们的地盘上贩毒
He was dealing in our territory.
而地盘属于你和你手下的保护范畴
The territory you and your men are charged with protecting.
出于礼节我才把他带过来的
I brought him here as a courtesy.
我缴的税还不够
So my tax dollars aren't enough
你和你的部落用  是吗
for you and your little tribe, huh?
你们这群混蛋还要来侵犯我的生意
Now you fuckers are going to encroach on my business?
操你妈
Fuck you.
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
我们为你们的住所
We pay for your houses...
你们的居留地
for your damn reservations,
你们的学校  你们的医保付钱
for your school, and your health care,
即使你们所有人
even when all of you were
都靠着赌场赚得盆满钵满  对吗
getting rich off your fucking casinos, right?
这个国家已经没了骨气
This country has lost its spine.
政治家把它给了一群蠢货和杂种
The politicians are giving it away to the mutts and the mongrels
而纯种美国人却只能挨饿
while good, pure-blooded Americans go hungry.
这已经不是一个国家了
This isn't a nation anymore.
而是他妈的施舍处
It's a fucking soup kitchen.
知道吗
And you know what?
我们都他妈没粥了
We're all out of fucking soup!
谢谢提醒
Thanks for the heads up.
你可以告诉普罗科特一切尽在掌控之中
You can tell Proctor that we've got it under control.
别在外人面前提他的名字
Don't use his name in front of outsiders.
他吗
Him?
他应该没有怎么注意
Yeah, I don't think he's paying too much attention.
你不会希望我再回到这的
You don't want me to come back here.
戴维斯酒馆
嘿  糖果
Hey, Sugar.
你消失了一年半
You disappear for a year and a half...
又像《圣经》里的神迹一样
you show up here looking like...
出现在这里
something out of the Bible,
而你能说的只有
and all you got to say for yourself is
"嘿  糖果"
"Hey, Sugar"?
你过得怎样
How you been?
跟我闲扯  闹呢
Small talk? Seriously?
有人杀了丽贝卡·鲍曼
Somebody killed Rebecca Bowman.
我知道
I know that.
这里所有人都知道
Everybody around here knows that.
但你怎么会知道
Now why do you know that?
这个...
Well...
我被当做嫌犯了
I guess I'm a suspect.
是你做的吗
Did you do it?
不是
No.
不能怪别人怀疑你
Look, it's a fair question.
看看你这样子
I mean, look at yourself.
你到底去哪里了
Where the hell have you been?
我得消失一段时间
I had to disappear for a while.
让头脑放空
Clear my head.
几天时间就能放空
You clear your head for a few days.
或许一周
A week maybe.
对你  可能要一个月
For you, maybe even a month.
可你却当了逃兵
But you, you went AWOL
忘了你的朋友  忘了你的...
and you forgot about your friends and you forgot about--
我没忘了贾伯
I didn't forget about Job.
你他妈躲起来对他有什么帮助
How the fuck was hiding away gonna help him?
你是来这里拿钱的
You here for your money?
不是
No.
但我需要一辆车
But I do need a car.
我只买了这个
Only thing I bought.
想着迅速逃离的话离会派上用场
Figured it might come in handy if I ever needed a quick exit.
现在怎么办
So what happens now?
不知道
I don't know.
但肯定会做点什么吧
But something, right?
对
Yeah.
做点什么
Something.
记住  胡德  你不是警长了
Remember, Hood, you're not the sheriff anymore.
我从来都不是
I never was.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
那人长什么样
What'd the other guy look like?
真他妈好笑
Very fucking funny.
其实我没开玩笑
Actually, I wasn't kidding.
他长什么样
What did he look like?
他看着像个妈的混蛋
He looked like a fucking asshole
把我手砸个稀巴烂的混蛋
smashing the shit out of my hands.
那家伙揍了你那么久
The guy stuck around long enough to walk all over your face
你都没看清吗
and you didn't even get a look?
那里很黑
It was dark.
没关系
Don't worry.
我有的是时间
I got time.
你回来了
You're back.
瑞贝卡的事我很难过
I'm sorry about Rebecca.
这和你有什么关系
What does this have to do with you?
没啥关系
Nothing.
那你怎么来了
And yet here you are.
有什么要告诉我的吗
Is there anything I should know?
你舅舅  他不是个好人
Your uncle, he's not a good man.
那让我和你住
Well, then let me live with you.
我也不是好人
I'm not a good man either.
我也想这么问你
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
你觉得我跟我侄女的死有关
You think I had anything to do with my niece's death?
可能不是你杀的  但他妈的是你害死了她
You may not have killed her, but you sure as shit got her killed.
你把她牵扯进来  迟早害死她
As soon as you took her in, it was only a matter of time.
对
Yeah.
你也许说得对
You may be right.
我会找到那个混蛋
I'm gonna find that son of a bitch.
可作为市长
But as a mayor,
要澄清真相却有点力不从心
I'm somewhat hampered in my ability to clarify matters.
你是怎么当上的
How'd you pull that off?
-因为没有对手  -想到了
- I ran unopposed. - Of course.
你会从哪查起
Where would you start?
从山麓的博迪克家族开始
The foothills. The Boedickers.
我听说他们家被烧光了
I heard they got burned down.
没错  可亚伦·博迪克还活着
It's true, but Aaron Boedicker is still alive.
你们没看到黄色警戒带吗
You guys, you did see the yellow tape here, right?
-警长  -没关系
- Sheriff. - It's fine.
这里的调查结束了
Our work is done here.
你在跟踪我吗  布罗克
You following me, Brock?
我  不  跟踪是我下属的活
Me? No. That's what deputies are for.
胡德是嫌犯吗
Is Hood a suspect?
他如果是  你肯定第一个知道吧
Well, if he was, you'd be the first to know it, wouldn't you?
不  胡德先生是本案的嫌疑人
No, Mr. Hood is a person of interest in this case,
而你俩都有嫌疑
which is something you two have in common.
警长  多加小心
Be careful, Sheriff.
我一直如此  市长先生
I always am, Mr. Mayor.
感觉又回到从前了吧
Just like old times, huh?
只是这次没人受伤
Except no one's bleeding.
还没而已
Yet.
柯特
Hey, Kurt.
别这样好吗  你打算一直无视我吗
Come on, bro. How long you gonna keep this up, man?
我可救了你一命  柯特
I saved your fucking life, Kurt.
要是瓦茨会怎么做
What do you think Watts would have done?
他一定会毙了你
He would have had you executed.
但我先发制人了
I took action before he could order it, that's it.
我在烧伤监护病房住了两个月
I was in the burn unit for two months.
我明白  我很抱歉
I know and I'm sorry,
但是你让我身处绝境
but you put me in an impossible situation
我必须表忠心啊
and I had to prove my loyalty to the cause.
你明白的
You know that.
来一块吃晚餐吧
Just come for dinner, man.
玛吉很希望你能来
Maggie would really love to see you.
我们也能好好谈谈
And we can work this out.
你总是说  再亲亲不过亲兄弟
Brothers before Brotherhood, that's what you always said.
我没有你这样的兄弟
You're not my brother.
什么  你他妈刚才说什么
What? What the fuck did you just say to me?
我是你和他们唯一的中间人  蠢货
I'm the only thing standing between them and you, asshole.
你最好给我记住了
You better fucking remember that!
-凯莉  -布罗克
- Hey, Carrie. - Hey, Brock.
开始有点样子了嘛
Wow, place is really starting to come together.
-谢谢  -不用  真挺好的
- Thanks. - No, looks good.
孩子们怎么样
How are the kids doing?
就那样吧  戈登的父母快把他们逼疯了
Oh, you know. Gordon's parents are driving them crazy.
有事吗  布罗克
Something on your mind, Brock?
那个  凯莉  不知道你听说没
Listen, Carrie, I don't know if you've heard, but...
胡德回来了
Hood is back.
看样子你应该不知道
Guess you haven't heard.
他一直住在山麓的一个小屋里
He's been living up in the foothills in a cabin.
他看上去很糟
He-- he looks rough.
我觉得你可能想知道
Just thought you'd want to know.
所以说一声
Yeah.
有事给我打电话  好吗
Call me if you need anything, all right?
好的
Okay.
-祝你今天过得开心  -谢谢
- Have a good day. - Thanks.
十八个月前
路易斯  一切正常吗
Lewis, is everything okay?
路易斯  请回答
Lewis, come in.
他妈的别动
Don't fucking move.
有什么好笑的
Something funny?
稍等片刻
Wait for it.
放下武器
Drop it!
是你
You.
正是
Me.
好久不见啊
Long time, huh?
坐下说如何
Why don't you take a seat?
这么多年你终于找到我了
You finally tracked me down after all these years.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫道尔顿
My name is Dalton.
-你是当兵的  -曾经是
- Are you military? - I was.
现在我们招募你这样的人
But now I recruit men like you.
培养他们成为精英队
I develop them for an elite unit.
什么队
What unit?
哪支部队的
What branch?
没错
Exactly.
那么
So...
这是复仇吗
this is revenge?
复仇
Revenge?
不算是
Not really.
贾伯在哪
Where's Job?
我他妈怎么知道
How the fuck would I know?
别这样  你知道套路的
No, no, no, no. You know how this works.
都是你教我的
You taught me.
手肘  脚背  膝盖
Elbows, insteps, knees.
我可以折磨你好几天
I can keep you alive for fucking days.
所以我要知道他在哪肯定会告诉你
I know, which is why if I knew something, I would tell you.
-胡说  -他不是我抓的
- Bullshit. - I didn't take him.
但抓他的人知道我想要他
But the man who did knew I would want him.
我付钱  他交出贾伯
I paid him his price and he handed over Job.
然后呢
Then what?
我把他交出去了
I turned him in.
我跟当权者两清了
I cleaned my slate with the powers that be.
-他们是谁  -得了吧
- And who are they? - Oh, come on.
别他妈装傻  你知道套路的
Don't be a fucking idiot. You know how this works.
名字和真人永远对不上号
Faces without names. Names without faces.
来吧  继续冲我左膝开枪吧
Go ahead. Go ahead shoot my left knee.
你知道这改变不了我说的事实
You know that it won't change what I'm saying.
我真不知道他们把他带到哪去了
I have no idea where they took him.
对  但你能找到他
No, but you can find him.
地下监狱  幽灵拘留所
Black sites, ghost detention centers.
你能拿到那些文件
You have access to those files.
已经不行了  国会听证会以后
Not anymore. After the congressional hearings,
圈子已经关上了  我不再是圈内人了
they closed the loop and I'm not in it.
胡扯  你就是圈内的重要人物
Bullshit. You are the fucking loop.
我以前是  20年前是
I was. That was 20 years ago.
今非昔比
Things change.
我们还说这事干什么
Why are we even having this conversation?
你明知贾伯已经死了
You know that Job is already dead.
不会  他有情报
No, he has intelligence.
-他是个重要线人 -20年前的情报
- He's a valuable asset. - His intelligence was 20 years old.
他是众人觊觎的战利品
He was a fucking trophy grab.
-被人用来炫耀的摆设  -被谁炫耀
- He was a head on somebody's wall. - Whose wall?
不重要了
Doesn't matter.
他已经死了
The man's dead.
你我心知肚明
You know it and I know it.
我们得走了
We got to go.
得赶紧走了
We got to go now.
看来我在圈子里还有些关系
I guess I'm still in certain loops.
快  快  快
Go, go, go.
他来找你了吗
Did he come to see you?
是
Yes.
但他已经不是那晚离开时的他了
But he's not the man that left that night.
不再是了
Not anymore.
他说他去哪了吗
Well, did he say where he's been?
没有
No.
那他说什么了吗
Did he say anything?
你认为他可能有贾伯的线索
You thought he might have a lead on Job?
听着  从他离开开始
Look, the day he left,
你就不该再期望能从他身上
that was the day you needed to stop looking to him
找到任何答案
for any answers.
你觉得贾伯还活着吗
You think Job's still alive?
我不知道
I don't know.
有时候我希望他死了
Sometimes I hope he isn't.
为什么
Why?
因为如果他还活着
Because if he is,
会让我们感觉自己更混蛋
it makes us even bigger assholes than we already are.
所以你们什么都没查到
So you got nothing.
没有
Nothing.
他要么不知道  要么不肯说
Either he didn't know or he wouldn't say.
他不知道
He didn't know.
这下我们永远都不会知道了
I guess we'll never know now.
真有必要杀他吗
Did you really have to kill him?
他不知道
He didn't know.
好吧
Okay.
下一步怎么办
What's our next play?
没有下一步了
We don't have one.
结束了
It's over.
不
No.
不能就这么放弃
We don't just give up.
我们别无选择
We have no choice.
那又怎样
So what?
-你不干了  -我们什么都没查到
- You're done? - We got nothing.
-那就去找啊  -什么都没有
- So we find something. - We've got nothing.
我不能就这么当他死了
I can't just leave him for dead.
你以为我愿意吗
Do you think I want to?!
你以为我什么都不想做吗
Don't you think I'd do anything?
道尔顿说得对
Dalton was right.
他说得对
He was right.
他把贾伯交出去的那一刻  贾伯就死了
Job was dead from the moment he handed him over.
你他妈去哪儿
Where the hell are you going?
他死了
He's dead.
有人在家吗
Anybody home?
有人吗
Hello?
爸爸
Daddy!
你好啊  小伙子
What's up, little man?
-你妈妈呢  -在楼上
- Where's your mommy? - Upstairs.
宝贝  我回来了
Yeah? Babe, I'm home.
来了
Coming.
天呐  你长大了
God, you got bigger.
现在多重  900多斤吗
What do you weigh, like 1,000 pounds?
-没有啦  -那有3米高了吧
- No. - What, are you, like 10 feet tall?
-没有  -好吧  也许明天就有了
- No. - Okay, maybe tomorrow.
你回来早了
You're home early.
对  我们今天把三季刊弄完了
Yeah, we finished the triquarterlies today.
那个亚洲佬给我们放假了
The slope gave everybody the day off.
真好
Nice.
锅里好香啊
It smells really good in here.
是炖肉和汤
It's just a pot roast and some soup.
-想不去想打篮球  -想
- You want to go shoot some hoops? - Yeah.
想啊  那我们去玩
Yeah? Maybe we'll go play
让妈妈做好晚饭叫我们好不好
and Mommy will let us know when dinner's ready.
别跟上次一样  又把我打败了  好不好
Don't beat me like you did last time, though, okay?
-对你老爹我放点水呗  -我会的
- Will you take it easy on your old man? - I will.
我肯定会打败你的
I'm pretty sure I'm gonna beat you, though.
我爱你
I love you.
如果是你  你会从哪着手
Where would you start?
山麓
The foothills.
博迪克家
The Boedickers.
我听说他们家被烧光了
I heard they got burned down.
亚伦·博迪克还活着
Aaron Boedicker is still alive.
你好啊  博迪克
Hey, Boedicker.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
四天前你在哪
Where were you four nights ago?
去你妈的
Fuck you.
我不会问你第二遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
我不知道你他妈想干什么
I don't know what the fuck you want,
但我屁都不会告诉你
but I'm not telling you shit.
我的手被你废了
You took my fucking hand.
丽贝卡·鲍曼在四天前被杀
Rebecca Bowman got killed four days ago.
那婊子自找的
Fucking bitch had it coming.
你看  你一说这种话
Yeah, see, when you say things like that,
就说明跟你有关系
that makes me think you had something to do with it.
想怎么折磨就来吧
You can torture me all you want,
你这个该死的虐待狂
you fucking sadist,
但我只会告诉你两件事
but I'm only gonna tell you two things.
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her
她死了我根本不在乎
and I don't give a shit she's dead.
没错  你确实知道些什么
Yeah, you do know something.
我知道的多了
Oh, I know a lot of things.
知道没有双手的人怎么擦屁股吗
You know how a guy with no hands wipes his ass?
我有个侄子
I've-- I've got a nephew.
艾尔杰
Eljay.
觉得自己是个摇滚明星
Thinks he's some kind of rock star.
他搞过那女的一段时间
He was fucking her for a while.
我去哪找他
Where do I find him?
我不知道他住哪
I don't know where he stays,
但他在一个叫蛇眼的鬼地方演夜场
but he plays nights at this shithole called Snake Eyes.
就在桥附近
It's off the connector.
如果我发现你撒谎
I find out you're lying to me,
我会回来废掉另一只手
I come back for the other hand.
这里不欢迎你
You're not welcome around here.
那我最好赶紧走吧
I better get going, then.
-你走不出去了  -赌什么的
- You're not going anywhere. - Want to bet?
看来你要被打成马蜂窝了
Looks like you're gonna end up full of holes.
那也是在我给你开个洞之后的事了
Not before I put one big fucking hole in you.
-行了  都住手  -该死
- Okay, let's break it up. -  God damn it.
马上
Now.
大多数警察都清楚  这山里不是好来的
Most cops know better than to come into the hills.
大多数混球都清楚  跟我顶嘴没好下场
Most assholes know better than to talk back to me.
这让我想起来  如果仔细找找
Something makes me think if I start looking,
可能会找到很多逮捕令上的人站在这呢
I'm gonna find a lot of outstanding warrants standing here.
你跟踪我来的
So you are following me around.
对  这还用问吗  顺便提一下
Yeah, I thought that was obvious by the way I pulled up
千钧一发的时候  是我救了你的小命
right at the nick of time to save your ass.
你来这里干什么  胡德
What are you doing here, Hood?
拜访一个老朋友
Just visiting an old friend.
我猜你有头绪了
I'm guessing you're working an angle.
丽贝卡是被她舅舅的某个对头杀死的
That Rebecca was killed by one of her uncle's enemies.
我什么头绪都没有
I'm not working any angles.
现在你是警长  烂摊子归你收拾
You're the sheriff now. This is your fucking mess.
对  而你仍然是这烂摊子里的疑犯
Yeah, and you're still a person of interest in this mess.
难道你要跟踪我一整天
Does that mean you're gonna follow me all fucking day?
胡德  你爱信不信
Yeah, well, believe it or not, Hood,
有那时间  我干点别的好不好
I've got better things to do with my time.
好
Good.
顺便说一句  不用谢
And you're welcome, by the way.
四天前